{"data":[{"question":"When we got to the spot the fire ____ all night.","a":"had be burning","b":"had been burning","c":"was burning","d":"burnt","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past ( The fire may continue burning after we got there) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When she arrived I ____ for two hours","a":"have been working","b":"had worked","c":"had been working","d":"worked","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past (I may continue working after she arrived) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When my mother and father got home I ____ watching TV for hours.","a":"have been","b":"was","c":"was being","d":"had been","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past (I watched TV before and may continue watching after parents got home) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When the boss arrived the secretary ____ letters for ages.","a":"has been typing","b":"had been typing","c":"had typed","d":"typed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past ( She typed before and may countinue typing after boss arrived) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"We ____ in the same block for years and we had never met.","a":"had been living","b":"are living","c":"have lived","d":"lived","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past ( We may coutinue living there) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"That picture ____ in the drawer for years when I found it.","a":"had lain","b":"had laid","c":"had been lying","d":"has been lying","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past (It lied there before and may continue lying there after I found) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"They ____ for two hours when I went to see the marathon.","a":"had run","b":"had been running","c":"were running","d":"have been running","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past ( They ran before and may continue running there after I arrived) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He ____ a wife for a long time, when I first met him.","a":"were wanting","b":"was wanting","c":"had been wanting","d":"had wanted","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past (He continued running there after met me) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She ____ for hours when they got home.","a":"had been asleep","b":"has been asleep","c":"had slept","d":"was sleeping","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past (She may continue feeling asleep after they got home) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When I went to prison, Luke ____ there for 10 years.","a":"has been","b":"was","c":"had been","d":"stayed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Continuous: \n+ Show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past (Luke was in prison and may continue being there after I arrived) \n+ Structure: S+ had + been +V_ing ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"15","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}